* [CMMC Services](#) Menu Toggle
* [Industries Served](#) Menu Toggle
* [Resources](#) Menu Toggle
* [About](#) Menu Toggle

Main Menu

* [CMMC Services](#) Menu Toggle
* [Industries Served](#) Menu Toggle
* [Resources](#) Menu Toggle
* [About](#) Menu Toggle

* [CMMC Services](#) Menu Toggle
* [Industries Served](#) Menu Toggle
* [Resources](#) Menu Toggle
* [About](#) Menu Toggle

Main Menu

* [CMMC Services](#) Menu Toggle
* [Industries Served](#) Menu Toggle
* [Resources](#) Menu Toggle
* [About](#) Menu Toggle

Privacy and Security Statement
==============================

The KLC Consulting, Inc. (“KLC”) Website is owned and provided by KLC. We respect your privacy and make every effort to control any information provided to us through any form of communications.

### Notice and Disclosure

Our Online Privacy Policy identifies how we treat your personal information. KLC collects individual information including, but not limited to a first name, last name, physical address, an e-mail address or other contact information. We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information for market research such as, your interests, demographics, and experience with our products.

In most cases, we do not require any personal information from you when visiting the KLC web sites. KLC does reserve the right to transfer information provided to us within KLC and with our business partners for marketing purposes. We do not sell personal information.

### Site Usage

You shall use the KLC web sites for lawful purposes only. In choosing to visit our web sites, you shall not post or transmit through these sites any information or material which violates or infringes, in any way, the rights of others, or which is unlawful, threatening, abusive, defamatory, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, vulgar, obscene, profane, harassing, or otherwise objectionable.

All material on the KLC web sites require KLC written approval before being used in any other form or any other location. Your use of the KLC web sites is at your own risk. If you are dissatisfied with any of the materials contained in these sites, please discontinue accessing and using these sites.

Our sites collect usage statistics but not personal information about the systems you are using or information such as email addresses. We do not use Cookies to collect any information about your browsing preferences.

You may choose whether or not to provide personal information to KLC and you may opt-in or opt-out of receiving information from KLC. Certain areas of our web sites may be inaccessible to you if you choose not to provide requested information.

If you chose to have a relationship with KLC, such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.

### Data Security

As a premiere security provider, we are extremely cognizant of the risk to collected information. Wherever your personal information may be held within KLC or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure. We continuously verify our security measures to keep our customer information secure.

### Data Accuracy

It is important to KLC to maintain accurate data. Any information you provide to us should be accurate. You have to option of inquiring about any data you have provided to us to ensure it is accurate. We may periodically request you verify the information provided to us. If ever you’d like to change your information, simply send an e-mail to privacy@klcconsulting.net.

### Liability

Under no circumstances will KLC, its suppliers or other third parties mentioned at, or involved in creating, producing, or delivering the site be liable for any direct, incidental, consequential, indirect, special or punitive damages whatsoever (including without limitation, costs and expenses of any type incurred, lost profits, lost data or programs, and business interruption) arising out of your access to, use, inability to use or the results of use of the site or any web sites linked to the site.

### Website Links

KLC’s site may contain links to other Web sites. KLC does not take any responsibility for any sites linked to our web sites with respect to the security and privacy measures used at those sites. You may link to the KLC web site.

### Changes

Any changes to the commitment to security and privacy of your information will be posted in the KLC Privacy Policy. KLC reserves the right to modify this statement at any time.

Check out our [YouTube](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7YHBN8MC2T2sVB411jC79Q) channel and [LinkedIn](https://www.linkedin.com/company/klc-consulting-inc-/) pages for the latest informational and educational resources for Cybersecurity Maturity Model Certification.

--------------------------------------------

Contact Us:

CMMC Services
-------------

Resources
---------

Industries Served
-----------------

About
-----

Copyright 2024 © [KLC Consulting](https://klcconsulting.net/ "KLC Consulting") All Rights Reserved | [Privacy Policy](https://klcconsulting.net/privacy-security-statement/) | [Site Map](https://klcconsulting.net/site-map/) | [Contact Us](https://klcconsulting.net/contact/) | [Website Design by MP Design](https://mpdesignonline.com/)

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Manage Cookie Consent

To provide the best experiences, we use technologies like cookies to store and/or access device information. Consenting to these technologies will allow us to process data such as browsing behavior or unique IDs on this site. Not consenting or withdrawing consent, may adversely affect certain features and functions.

Functional  Functional Always active

The technical storage or access is strictly necessary for the legitimate purpose of enabling the use of a specific service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user, or for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network.

Preferences  Preferences

The technical storage or access is necessary for the legitimate purpose of storing preferences that are not requested by the subscriber or user.

Statistics  Statistics

The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for statistical purposes. The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for anonymous statistical purposes. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, information stored or retrieved for this purpose alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

Marketing  Marketing

The technical storage or access is required to create user profiles to send advertising, or to track the user on a website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.

Accept Deny View preferences Save preferences [View preferences](#)

Manage consent

Scroll to Top
